We'll be right back.
Almost to Luffy.
Gather at the Courthouse Plaza.
We'll be right back.
What?
No!
Gamora can't see!
His retinas were damaged in that last attack.
He's blind!
What's that?
Gamora!
You can't see anything?
It started running like crazy!
Don't just stand there, shoot it!
We gotta stop that thing!
We can't let it go any further!
Fire the transporter!
Gamora, don't do this!
Please stop!
You're in no shape to go on!
You'll kill yourself!
He said that he made a promise to Sodom!
He told Sodom, leave the rest to me!
I'll take on your share and carry everyone the rest of the way!
Gamora!
They were in its stomach?
I'm full already.
Couldn't eat another bite.
Let's take him with us.
It's backup food.
Big bro!
Come here quick!
Some pirates gave Sodom and Gamora a serious beating!
You pirates have got a lot of nerve.
Never touch my family!
Hey!
Take it easy, you two!
You're still injured!
This is no time for a dance party!
Ha ha ha!
We're headed straight for a dead end!
He'll crash into it and die!
Gamora!
Stop it!
You'll never make it!
Stop!
A dead end!
I don't see one, do you?
Nope!
Can't say I see anything of the sort!
A dead end!
It's the courthouse!
He did it!
Yeah!
You made it!
Gamora!
All units!
The King Bull carrying the pirates broke through Block D and they are now at the courthouse plaza!
I repeat!
The King Bull carrying the pirates broke through!
Look at this, Fogfreed!
A golden transponder snail!
Having this little gadget is the same as having the authority to issue a buster call!
Was someone even higher up than that, Admiral Aokiji entrusted it to me!
The question is if and when will I use it?
Hmm...
Just you wait.
Once I revive the ancient weapons, this won't just be something that's on loan to me.
I'll carry it of my own accord, along with the power to control an army.
I will now initiate a buster call!
All ships may commence attack at once!
Target every last thing on this island of archaeology and turn Ohara into ash!
With a single push of a button, an entire island will disappear!
Authority can be a weapon unto itself!
Oh, the power!
Team Spondom!
That was close!
What's wrong with you?
Can't you even knock?
I almost accidentally hit the button!
I'm terribly sorry, sir, but I'm afraid we've got an emergency here.
There's an urgent call from Innie's Lobby's main island!
Idiots!
If there's an emergency, why didn't they just call my room directly?
What the...
Hey!
Why is the receiver off the hook?
This always happens!
Who's responsible?
Well, either way, you were saying something about an emergency, weren't you?
Yes, sir!
Sponda!
Hey, Miss Robin!
It seems we have an urgent report coming in from the marines down at the main island.
Knowing what it's likely about, I wouldn't call it an... emergency, exactly.
Your friends tried their best, but only managed to take down five of our soldiers.
I wonder how they were ultimately defeated.
Did some of my other men bring them down?
Or was it the giant gatekeeping team of Oimo and Kashi?
So many possibilities.
Why don't we listen to the report about those idiots who defied the world government?
And learn their fate together?
You're such a scumbag!
Shut up, you lowlife!
This is Spondum.
I understand you have a report.
Chief Spondum!
Finally!
Thank goodness!
I tried your direct line, but I couldn't get through.
I'm...
I'm not really sure where to begin.
Calm down.
Take it easy.
It's the Straw Hats, right?
Yes.
What about them?
Whoa.
Hold on.
Listen.
Take up from where your last report ended.
Give me the gritty details, loudly and clearly.
Right.
The intruders...
Did you accidentally kill them?
Pity.
It's their fault for being such weaklings.
The intruders consist of about 60 pirates.
They've pushed their way all the way through the main island and have reached the courthouse plaza.
We can't stop them, sir!
All personnel on any slobby's main island, head to the courthouse plaza immediately!
You did a good job, Gamora.
I swear everything you two did will not be in vain.
All right, we're breaking in!
It's time to say big bro breaking!
Yeah!
I repeat!
The pirates have reached the courthouse plaza!
Can you see Luffy?
Nope.
But whether he's up on the roof or not, it's not exactly like we can just jump up after him.
That's true.
How much we can do.
How many members of CP9 did you see up there?
It was just that one big guy with the bullhorns.
It's hard to believe that Robin, Frankie, all of them are right behind those doors.
In any case, we need to catch up with Luffy.
Then we can save Robin together!
Hurry!
Get to the courthouse!
The drawbridge isn't down yet!
Corner them!
Whoa!
That frog's awesome!
That's the same bow that took out Gamora!
Who threw it?
Whoa!
There's three of them!
And they're running away!
Why are they running away?
They're the ones that attacked first!
Idiot cook!
We can't go around chasing every enemy that runs off like that!
It's a waste of time!
Oh, pipe down!
It's confirmation!
Some of them need to be chased, understand?
To find out who we're up against.
Whoa!
Where's this guy?
He must have superhuman strength to swing something like that around.
You think he's part of some special unit, like those guard dogs?
There are probably more of them hiding out there somewhere.
Let's be careful.
We need to get moving.
It looks like the reinforcements have arrived.
Surround them!
There's no way they'll be able to open those heavy stone doors!
We'll have them cornered! Move it!
He's right.
Now that I think about it, how...
Are we gonna open those big stones?
We're going in first! Stay close! Don't fall behind!
He... he cut right through them! Like it was nothing!
Hey, Zombai! Let's split up!
We need to charge both of those towers!
Because each side has a lever to open up that drawbridge!
Yeah! Good thinking! I'm on it!
Right! Looks like we need to split into three teams!
Most of you go with Kiwi and Mozu, the rest are with me!
We'll crack some heads in that courthouse!
Good luck, everyone!
Move!
Also, the gatekeepers of the main island front gate, Oimo and Kashi, have joined up with the pirates!
They're currently destroying the central part of the main island!
We are the way!
We'll see you next time.
You know, truth is, I'm glad I met you guys when I did.
And why is that?
Because thanks to you, I won't ever lose my friends.
Ridiculous. You certainly are full of hot air.
Now, gum gum!
On the next, One Piece, everything is to protect my friends.
Second gear activated.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!